

CONTACT

™ info@resumekraft.com

202-555-0120

Chicago, Illinois, US

in linkedin.com/resumekraft

SKILLS

Python

SQL

Tableau

Machine Learning

AWS

AWARDS

IBM Champion Learner -Bronze 2020

Completed 150+ hours of learning in 2020, thereby earning the IBM Champion Learner -Bronze badge.

Client Funded Award

Received 'Client Funded Award' in 2019 for demonstrating the IBM Practice: Put the client first.

Manager's Choice Award Received 'Manager's Choice Award' in 2017, 2018 and 2019.

KEVIN HARRY

DATA SCIENTIST

SUMMARY

I am a full stack Data Scientist - motivated, upbeat and resilient, with experience in both academic and corporate settings. Having been involved in the development of an analytics engine, I am thoroughly experienced in the development and use of data ingestion, data analysis, machine learning and data visualization tools. In addition to my technical skills, I am also a strong communicator and have experience working in team-based environments.

EXPERIENCE

Data Scientist

Sep 2021 - Present

Thinkbumblebee Analytics Private Ltd.

Besides leading the Client Management team, I'm actively involved in the development, optimization and maintenance of data science and data engineering features of the product, Propellor.ai

Teacher Whitehat Jr.

Sep 2020 - Jun 2021

I taught coding (game development, app development, basics of AI) to high school students as an online course.

Application Developer IBM India Private Ltd.

Aug 2015 - Oct 2020

I worked as an Oracle Apps Technical mainly concerned with application development, customization and implementation using SQL, Oracle E-Business Suite and Hyperion.

EDUCATION

PG Diploma in Data Science San Jose State University

Aug 2019 - Aug 2020

Completed the rigorous online PG Diploma (Data Science) from IIIT-Bangalore, with CGPA of 3.34 (out of 4), in 2020.

Bachelor of Technology Northeastern University

Sep 2011 - May 2015

- Completed B.Tech. (Civil Engineering) from TKM College of Engg., Kerala University in 2015 with CGPA of 8.6.
- Procured GATE Score of 664(AIR of 973) at GATE-2015.

PROJECTS

Propellor Data Science Sr. Data Scientist, Thinkbumble Analytics Private Ltd. Sep 2021 - Present